(Hongik University Station)
(A street where the heat never cools down)
(Every street is packed with hip vibes.)
(Hongik University)
It's been ages since I came to Hongdae.
I wonder...
who has ties to this neighborhood.
Are they musicians?
Is that so? Are we meeting musicians today?
To have ties to this neighborhood, they should be...
- somewhat...
- Who are they?
You guys didn't get any information about this week's Whenever Friends?
- No, not today.
- No.
I don't bother trying to figure out who's joining us every week.
Sometimes, I just happen to find out by chance.
- Same here. It also happens...
- As for Yeon Seok,
he does try to figure out who's joining us.
- He does try to figure that out.
- Today,
I wasn't able to get any information.
You see Jae Seok often, right?
- I saw him yesterday too.
- Right.
My gosh. I know for sure that he's not going to welcome me.
(Laughing)
He's going to get sick of me as soon as I walk in.
- Good presents...
- It could've been awful.
- Who are they? What?
- They're here.
- Who are they?
- A musician...
and a model.
- Really?
- But this model is funny.
- Come on. It's Joo Woo Jae.
- Hello.
(Today's Whenever Friends: Joo Woo Jae...)
(and John Park)
- Hello.
- My gosh.
- Nice to meet you.
- What's Woo Jae doing here?
- See? Didn't I tell you?
- Hello.
- He won't be excited.
- Why...
Why did you want me...
- to keep this a secret?
- What's he...
Why...
Why did you want me...
- to keep this a secret?
- What's he doing at my workplace?
At your workplace?
- We worked together yesterday.
- Hey, Park John.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
(I'll welcome my dear colleague, Park John.)
- It's been a while.
- What brings you here, Woo Jae?
I was in the neighborhood of my alma mater.
- So I dropped by.
- You went to Hongik University.
- I see.
- Woo Jae went to Hongik University.
That's why we're here today.
Sit next to Jae Seok.
Why don't you sit next to him?
I always sit next to him.
- Let me explain. I...
- I was with him all day yesterday.
- It's the farthest spot from you.
- Right.
- Hey.
- Actually,
I made a promise to myself this year.
- What promise?
- What was the promise?
That I would never appear on Jae Seok's other shows...
as a guest.
He never treats me like a guest.
- How did you end up here today?
- Today...
Actually, three weeks ago,
- he was on "Sixth Sense."
- Right.
When we were filming the show together,
he never asked me a question even though I was a guest.
- So...
- Woo Jae...
I had to find ways to tell my stories on the show.
Yes. Back then, he...
I swore I'd never appear on another show of his.
Then how did you end up on our show?
Well, I'm here with John today.
- John. It's been ages.
- Park.
- Yes. You've been well, right?
- You know?
- We met on "Hangout with Yoo."
- Yes.
- We filmed it a long time ago.
- That was...
- the last time. It's been so long.
- We...
John, you've been posting videos on your YouTube channel regularly.
- Yes.
- You've done many projects.
That's right.
- You recently sang RESCENE's song.
- Yes.
- You did, didn't you?
- Right. I did a cover song.
(RESCENE's "LOVE ATTACK," the legend of chart-climbers)
(He reimagined the track with a stylish arrangement.)
(He sang aespa's "Whiplash" with his super low-pitched voice.)
(Crushing the girl groups' songs with his unique deep voice)
(His arrangements are amazing,)
(but he truly shines when he's singing his own songs.)
(John Park with the unbeatable voice)
- He killed it as expected.
- John was amazing as expected.
John, do you have any ties to this neighborhood, Hongdae?
Actually, I've mostly been working in Gangnam.
You mostly work in Gangnam.
- Right. I think...
- Yes.
- You sound like a real local.
- the only tie to Hongdae...
must be Woo Jae with his alma mater.
But he mostly hangs out in Gangnam too.
- That's true.
- Yes.
But I still went to Hongik University.
- You went to college here.
- I see.
And I lived here for 6 to 7 years.
This was my turf.
- I see.
- I lived here for a long time.
Jae Seok. It's your gaze. I can already tell that...
you're not treating me like a guest.
Well, you're here as a guest.
That explains my behavior.
- Okay.
- As for me,
I come to Hongdae occasionally to work on music.
- To work on music?
- Yes.
I come here to record songs.
A lot of musicians are based here too.
John is getting recognized a lot for his arrangements these days.
Isn't that what you're focusing on these days?
- I'm doing my best.
- Right.
- Really?
- And what do you know about that?
Are you serious? That's your question?
- Your question to your guest?
- Listen.
- "What do you know about that?"
- When I ask you questions,
- you don't answer me.
- Unbelievable.
- Is the host supposed to sound...
- Right.
that rude when asking questions?
"What do you know about that?"
- He's definitely picking on you.
- Listen.
I'm not picking on him. Wasn't that a fair question?
I should point out your attitude toward him.
- You look quite disrespectful.
- He's just...
Okay.
You must have taken it the wrong way...
because of my attitude.
- But I was just asking you.
- Seriously.
What should I do with that smug face?
Seriously. Everything that comes out of his mouth sounds insincere.
- You think so?
- I hate that smug face.
- You can feel that?
- Yes.
- I get it. We just met yesterday.
- It's impossible to hide that.
We saw each other yesterday too.
And Park is a huge fan of naengmyeon.
- Yes.
- He loves naengmyeon.
He likes noodles?
- Right.
He loves naengmyeon.
He can guess the restaurants just by looking at...
the high-angle shots of naengmyeon.
I went through a naengmyeon phase.
- But not anymore?
- No.
- I like naengmyeon.
- Okay.
- You don't love it?
- But I'm not that crazy about it.
But it looked like you were.
That phase is over now.
It sounds like you got sick of naengmyeon.
My love for naengmyeon has faded a bit.
- I see. It's faded.
- Yes.
I used to love naengmyeon.
When I enter a naengmyeon restaurant,
other customers talk in whispers.
- "He's here."
- And the owner...
- and the workers...
- They get nervous.
The servers would suddenly go into the kitchen.
"He's here."
- I'm here today with Park.
- Yes.
People might think that John and I have never crossed paths.
But have you?
I told Park that...
I was his biggest fan. After telling him that,
I went to see him perform literarally dozens of times.
- Really?
- Yes.
He goes to too many shows for no good reason.
- So don't think it's that special.
- And...
I bet he can't understand the shows on the first watch.
So he watches them dozens of times.
You only need to watch them once or twice to follow the shows.
Why do you watch them dozens of times?
Performances are not meant to be understood.
- They must be felt.
- Why...
- I get to feel them several times.
- Then I don't get...
why he watches them dozens of times. Why does he do that?
- Why are you...
- Because I like his shows.
- watching them dozens of times?
- Because I like them.
Have you watched our show before?
- I watched a lot of the episodes.
- Me too.
Did you watch the game parts too?
I did. It seemed you mostly handled everything.
(He's unbelievable.)
- You're spot on.
- So...
- Jae Seok...
- Yes.
handles big things...
while ruining all these small things.
With that logic, he only handles small things?
No. That's not what I meant.
- That was quite rude.
- That's not what I meant.
- That's what you meant.
- I mean...
- That's not what I meant.
- You misspoke.
Jae Seok is the big-picture guy.
But Yeon Seok is so detailed.
- He can handle every game.
- Right, he's detailed.
Everyone must do well for us to succeed here.
He chokes in actual games.
- Right. During the games...
- You think I choke in actual games?
- Your eyes...
- That's hard to pull off.
Park, are you good at these games?
I'm crazy about games.
- Really?
- You're crazy about games now?
You know those arcade games?
- Or board games.
- Or brain games.
(He's crazy about all types of games.)
Brain games.
- But when I watched you...
- Do you have a knack for them?
play these games on Whenever Possible,
it made me wonder...
if these silly games really brought...
that much joy.
That's why...
I don't think I'll be that happy even if we succeed today.
I don't think I'll be that heartbroken even if we fail.
- That's what you think will happen?
- But once he starts playing...
You just had to play with table tennis balls...
- for the games.
- Gosh.
- He's...
- He thinks it will be easy to win.
When you watch our show at home, our games do look very silly.
- But these games drive you crazy.
- That's right.
You should experience it yourself.
- It doesn't go as planned.
- Right.
Anyway, we're here in Hongdae because of Woo Jae today.
Let's find out about the Whenever Guests we'll meet.
Her name is Lee Bit Na.
"My husband is the master salesman..."
"who can sell anything out by winning people over..."
"in front of cameras under the fancy lights."
(Surprised)
"He's busy passing down his secrets..."
"to his juniors."
"I've never had the chance to see him at work."
"I'd love to check out his workplace with your show."
Is he a professor?
But it said fancy lights.
- And he sells everything out.
- Sells everything out?
- Sales?
- Everything?
The master salesman?
- Livestream shopping is trendy now.
- A show host?
- Is it something like that?
- Yes.
He's passing down his secret now. He might work at an academy.
Could that be it?
- Well, yes. That could be it.
- That could be it. A teacher.
- Where is it?
- Let me look it up.
I know where it is just by looking at the address.
- Really?
- Do you know where it is?
- I see. Yes.
- So...
- do you know how to get there?
- Yes.
- Then why don't you...
- Please guide us.
- You don't need it, right?
- Why don't you be our guide today?
- You don't need the GPS, right?
- No.
It's 400-10 in Seogyo-dong.
We should follow Navi Joo today...
- instead of Navi Yoo.
- Navi Joo?
It looks like he's looking it up on the GPS.
- Wait.
- What's he doing?
(Looking busy)
Come on.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Yeon Seok would've done it if you were going to look it up.
(Navi Joo will be in charge of guiding them.)
- He could've done it then.
- Let's go.
We can just go now?
I haven't been here in ages.
(Current time, 11:15pm)
What did you major in college, Woo Jae?
- Mechanical Engineering.
- That was your major.
(The former engineering major)
Actually, I withdrew from my school...
- You must've been smart.
- in the second semester...
of my fourth year.
- Why?
- So I never graduated.
That's when I made my debut.
I made my debut when I took time off from college.
- You only had one semester left?
- You were so close.
Yes. I was almost done.
Can't you go back for one semester and graduate?
I thought about doing that.
But I learned everything I needed.
- I don't need to go back.
- But still.
You weren't tenacious more than anything.
(Chuckling)
- Out of the four years, - That makes you a quitter.
- I finished three and a half years.
- Well,
- you didn't see it through.
- Didn't you...
- drop out of your school as well?
- You should've followed through.
Didn't you drop out of Seoul Institute of the Arts?
- I...
- I don't think he's listening.
- In my fourth year...
- You weren't tenacious at all.
- Woo Jae, you can't quit like that.
- My gosh.
This whole place is newly built.
This wasn't here when I was in school.
That's how you go up into the campus.
I've never been to this side of the campus.
I've driven past the main entrance a lot of times.
- But I've never gone in.
- Right.
They set up the entire campus here.
This is amazing.
My gosh.
I see. This is where the path leads to.
When we turn left here,
- we'll reach Sangsu Station.
- Okay.
Then making a right turn there...
We know that much about this neighborhood.
(Chuckling)
- Bo Pil.
- I mean...
Never ask me to appear on this show again.
I get treated better than this on other shows.
- We have to cross here.
- Turning left... Okay.
The light turned green right away.
- It's perfect.
- Hello.
Hello.
Goodness, they're probably my juniors.
- These young students...
- But...
you didn't graduate, did you?
- Right. They're not your juniors.
- Exactly.
- They're not, right?
- They're just strangers.
I shouldn't have said anything.
(Laughing)
Over there. Look.
I used to study in the library...
- after class.
- Okay.
Then I'd head over there, open a can of beer,
- You'd sit over there and drink?
- and drink with my seniors.
(It brings back old memories.)
I didn't have any money back then.
John, what were your college days like?
- I studied abroad for college.
- Yes.
(A prestigious university, Northwestern University)
- And...
- You graduated, right?
I also withdrew from my school while taking some time off.
- All of you dropped out.
- Here's why.
- But...
- He had to drop out.
- Because...
- It's not easy...
to stay in school while working.
Right. I auditioned for the TV show when I was still in school.
After appearing on "Superstar K,"
moving to Korea made the most sense.
And I dropped out.
- Didn't you debut 20 years ago?
- Right.
- I debuted 16 years ago.
- It was 16 years ago?
- It's been a long time.
- Right.
It doesn't feel that long ago.
- Right?
- Park. How long...
have you been married?
It's been four years now.
- Four years. Yes.
- It's already been that long?
- My child is three years old.
- You have a child?
- Yes, he does.
- He does.
- Really?
- How old is your daughter?
- She's 35 months old. Yes.
- She's 35 months old?
(She's growing up while listening to this beautiful voice.)
(Adorable)
Yeon Seok.
You were in the music video of "Things to Do Tomorrow."
How do you remember that?
- I'm Jong Shin's fan too.
- Really?
You filmed the music video of "Things to Do Tomorrow."
- I filmed that when I was a rookie.
- That was... Yes.
- Later, I...
- You...
filmed it again for Monthly Yoon Jong Shin.
- Sung Si Kyung sang the song.
- Yes.
- Right. Yes, you did.
- I was in that music video too.
I can't believe you remember that.
Because back then,
this music video was huge among the fans.
It was just you in the video,
- getting ready for the breakup.
- Right.
By that time, it had been...
- I had just made my debut.
- Right?
It had only been a few years.
My goodness. I'm seeing a lot of great restaurants.
That's a kebab restaurant.
This is the start of the famous street.
The Street You Want to Walk.
I know.
- I was talking to Yeon Seok.
- You...
- I was talking to these two guys.
- What?
- I'm sorry to interrupt.
- This place is...
But I've been coming here since the 90s.
- The Street You Want to Walk.
- I've been coming here...
- since the 90s.
- Oh, the food alley.
When you guys were...
- in school, - Yes.
I used to come here and dance at a rock cafe.
- A rock cafe?
Yes. So...
I came here even before you set foot in this neighborhood.
- I'm practically from here.
- Of course.
- I know that.
- Is there a club...
where the rock cafe used to be?
- Is it in the same spot?
- Right.
- All the rock cafes were...
- That's right.
on the main street.
Wasn't everything around...
- the three-way intersection?
- Right. That was the spot.
- They probably won't come.
- Right here.
- So...
- This used to be the main store...
when I was living alone here.
- Coa Store.
- We're not here...
to help you take a trip down memory lane.
I was talking.
- This is Coa Store.
- He keeps pointing out...
- places he ate at...
- Coa Store.
- and the grocery store...
- Come on.
I'm understanding when it comes to most things.
I didn't say anything when we were on campus.
He even mentioned the vegetable store he shopped from.
- I see.
- The grocery store.
- Gosh, this place.
- When you built this neighborhood.
Should I do this too?
Should I tell you about the places I visited when I came here for fun?
- On top of the rock cafes?
- When you had to wait...
at a table for your friends?
I only went to rock cafes.
- Sixteen.
- Sixteen. Then...
- fifteen should be around here.
- It's right here. Fifteen.
- This must be the building.
- Yes.
- Second floor in this building.
- Yes, this is the place.
- This is the place?
- Is he a dance instructor...
who runs a dance studio?
(Who's the Whenever Guest under the fancy lights?)
- I think this is the place.
- It's right here.
Hello.
(Screaming)
- Hold on.
- Oh, my.
It's you, right?
- Hello.
- Hi.
- My gosh. This place...
- Hello.
(First Whenever Guest: Lee Bit Na...)
(and Go Yeon Wook)
Hello.
This looks like a lecture room.
It said "Academy" on the sign.
- It said "Academy" on the sign.
- I see.
This is the academy for show hosts.
- I was right. Yes.
- Our guess was right.
- Bit Na, you wrote to the show.
- Yes.
- I wrote it. Yes, I did it.
- You wrote the letter, right?
Are both of you from this industry?
I'd love to work in this industry,
- but I'm not.
- I see.
But my husband can sell everything out...
- even to this day.
- I see.
I asked because they looked familiar.
When you actively appeared on TV as a show host,
you must've focused on a specific line of products.
I mostly dealt with home appliances, insurance policies, and so on.
Or daily supplies.
I don't appear on TV anymore.
I only run this academy now.
- You only run this academy.
- Right.
I've been running the academy for a while now.
It's been about seven years.
- That's a long time.
- I'm going into my eighth year.
So you run an academy for show hosts.
If you had to...
sell our show to the viewers, how would you do it?
How would you introduce our show as a product?
- As a product?
- I bet the staff asked for this.
Requests like this...
- He's becoming one of them.
- My gosh. Just now,
- He hates it.
- I got the chills.
This is the exact kind of question from the staff.
- It didn't come from them.
- It didn't?
- No.
- My gosh.
You're not wearing an earpiece, right?
Out of all the lines I've heard for the past few years,
- that sounded the most scripted.
- Right. The staff would ask that.
- I thought he was their puppet.
- I was shocked.
But I'm curious.
So sell Whenever Possible? This is...
- the 5th season.
- It's our 5th season.
- Season Five.
- Yes.
On home-shopping networks, it's important to emphasize...
- the number of seasons.
- Right.
- That's right.
- That could be a keyword.
- They promote the same products...
- That's right.
- once the products get a makeover.
After the makeover,
we can't criticize...
- You can't criticize them.
- the older versions.
The customers who bought the older versions...
- Right. They would.
- would get upset.
The products were great, to begin with.
But they got upgraded.
That's how we need to do the promo.
- Their quality improved.
- That's right.
- That's very important.
- Yes.
- Did your show's ratings go up...
- So I...
- throughout the five seasons?
- Yes.
That's good to hear.
(Season 4 was great, but Season 5 is more entertaining.)
I think you're lying.
- Bit Na, you wrote to our show.
- Yes.
- Right.
- What made you write the letter?
My husband opened a new academy.
But I could never visit because he didn't let me.
- Here?
- Right.
Not once for eight years?
- Right. I had never been here.
- Right.
- Then is this your first time here?
- I'm serious.
- This is my first time ever.
- Really?
- I really wanted to come here.
I thought I'd be able to...
if you guys came with me. That's why I wrote to your show.
Did you not let her come...
- on purpose?
- I see.
- Oh, that.
- That's not it, right?
- This is my workplace.
- Right.
She already has so much to do at home.
- We have two sons.
- I see.
Raising them is hard enough.
I felt bad to ask her to come and help out at the academy.
Now that my academy has started to have more students,
during the entrance exam season,
I have to stay here and work nonstop for 14 hours.
I skip meals to teach my students.
- I once got kidney stones.
- You must be very busy.
And I had to break up the stones.
Why are you suddenly telling us about your health problems?
You worked so hard that you even got kidney stones?
- Yes. This job affects my health.
- I see.
I can understand Bit Na's perspective too.
I mean, she's very busy at home too. She has a tough job.
- She's super busy.
- Right.
- No? Let's hear from Bit Na then.
- Right. Seriously.
He just says these things when he meets people outside.
He just says these things.
- I'm sure he had health problems.
- He's just exaggerating them.
But he had to mention the kidney stones.
Bringing up the kidney stones when his wife is right here...
- Right. He wanted to emphasize...
- "I have a tough job."
that he was working really hard too.
- "This job is exhausting."
- It is exhausting, right?
- It must be.
- I'm sure it is.
- Right.
- Yes.
Both of them are complaining while looking ahead.
- They didn't look at each other.
- That would be uncomfortable.
- Right. Like this.
- It'd be uncomfortable that way.
So they're looking ahead while complaining.
Could we ask how you guys met?
- We met at a show host academy.
- I see.
I was wondering if she also prepared to become a show host.
I wanted to be a show host.
- She was much better than me.
- But I couldn't be one.
- How?
- My gosh.
I couldn't seem to pass the exams. They keep rejecting me.
- But you kept taking the exams.
- Yes. I did.
I was shy. So when I was practicing alone...
in the academy,
she came to me and said, "What are you doing?"
"Why are you practicing? You just wing it on the spot."
She had this cool girl vibe.
(Her confidence charmed him.)
She never got nervous on stage.
She teased him about practicing.
- Right.
- Is that why she never passed?
- I'm sorry.
- I very much regret it.
- My gosh.
- How could you be so rude to her?
- What was that?
After hearing their story,
- I thought it could be relevant.
- I regret not practicing.
But that was true.
He practiced much harder than I did.
I just focused on having more fun with it.
- You were spot on.
- My gosh, no.
I'll work harder now.
- I'll engrave that on my bones.
- I'm sorry.
- Bit Na holds grudges too.
- I'll do my best now.
- She must already be stressed...
- That's...
- from raising two boys.
- Right.
- It must be really stressful.
- I have to work until midnight.
My gosh. I was awful.
(Oh, no...)
Woo Jae isn't married.
- He doesn't know these hardships.
- Right.
- I lack empathy. That's true.
It's something only we can understand.
- Only John and I can understand it.
- Yes.
- I didn't say a word.
- Exactly.
- You're clearly wiser.
- We didn't say a thing.
I...
I have no choice but to kill it at the game today.
The only way to fix Bit Na's bad mood now is...
- I must do well with the game.
- doing well with the game...
and making it to Round Three. Right?
- Yes.
- I totally shot myself in the foot.
All right. Let's start with Round One.
We don't know what we're going to play today.
My gosh. That's...
(What present could bring a dopamine boost to their exhausting life?)
"This present is for the students..."
"who are studying all night long to become master salespeople."
"A coffee machine and capsules from Nespresso."
It's definitely...
A coffee machine.
- They brought a lot of capsules.
- This is great.
Nice.
- I really needed these.
- You need them, right?
- Right. Wait, you don't have one?
- No, I don't.
- I don't have one.
- You totally need this.
What's the first game?
(Bouncy Reflector)
(Hold the reflector...)
(with a box of tissue on it.)
(Bounce the box and get it to stand upright in a relay format.)
(But they only have 10 seconds.)
It's a real reflector.
(Light reflectors used for filming)
We'll use this.
- Then make it stand upright?
- Yes.
I see. We have to make it stand upright?
- My gosh...
- The four of you must succeed...
within ten seconds.
- You must do it in one go.
- We have to...
Wait.
You can do this.
If we fail, do we start over?
- Or whoever fails can try again?
- Right, they can try again.
My gosh, this isn't easy.
- You did it.
- I got it.
- I can start like this. Hold on.
- Wait.
Like this.
(Success)
Yeon Seok, it's easier when you put it on the edge.
- We didn't start yet.
- Put it on the edge.
- It's easier on the edge.
- On the edge?
(Success)
Right? Yes.
- Put it on the edge and be gentle.
- It looks like...
Just like this. I got it.
- It has to absorb the shock.
- Ten seconds?
Yes.
I think we can pass Round One.
- Around here.
- Are you ready?
I'm ready.
You seem confident today.
I got this. This game...
Well, you're always great during practice.
Hey, that was...
We might fail even with good teamwork.
It's not easy for the four of us to succeed together.
Ten seconds... The time limit might be the problem.
- Ten seconds?
- Yes.
- But we can keep trying, right?
- Ten seconds?
Right. You can keep trying.
Can we try it?
- Let's practice.
- It's a practice round.
- All right. Ready...
- Yeon Seok should go first.
- Yeon Seok goes first.
- Go.
(Practice)
This isn't good. But I can try again.
- Okay. Like this.
- Okay.
Okay.
Two, one.
See? The time limit is the problem.
(They succeeded, but they went over the time.)
- The time limit is the problem.
- We have to do it faster.
- That's the problem.
- You guys have to do it faster.
- Okay.
- That's the problem.
- All right.
- Let's give it a try.
- Let's try it for the first time.
- Yes.
- I'll go first.
- Great.
Here we go.
- We have to do well.
- Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
(1st try)
Try again.
(In the blink of an eye, the last player is up.)
Come on, Jae Seok.
(If Jae Seok succeeds, they'll pass Round 1 right away.)
Four, three...
- Okay.
- Success.
- They did it?
- Wait, we did it?
- That's it.
- We did it?
- You guys did it?
- We did it.
- On our first try.
- Round One, success.
- Success.
- Yes.
- What?
This is great.
You know what?
- We do well in Rounds 1 and 2.
- The thing is,
- we made it to Round Two...
- Yes.
on our second try in previous episodes.
But Round Three...
The game gets really hard for Round Three.
So we need to be careful when we pass the rounds...
- too early in the mission.
- I see.
All right.
- We passed Round 1 on our 1st try.
- Round 1.
You must decide if you want to go for Round Two or not.
One, two, three.
Go!
- Great.
- We have many tries left.
"We need clean air for our overworked throat."
"A Dyson air purifier."
(A must-have for a home with kids and an academy with students)
(Surprised)
- That's a great product.
- I love it.
(Getting up to welcome the present)
- They're so happy.
- You guys look happy.
Yes. This is great.
- I really want to win it for them.
- Round Two...
All right.
(Round 2: The box gets thinner.)
(Round 1)
(The width is almost halved.)
- That's for Round Two?
- Okay.
- Or it could be two boxes.
- It's heavy too.
You know...
(It's gotten much heavier.)
- Gosh, this is...
- You were an engineering major.
Should we put the wider side on it? Or the narrower side?
- It should be the wider side.
- This side?
- Yes. Here's why.
- Okay.
- When we toss it up, - Yes.
the box is more likely to shake in the air...
than when we toss it up with the narrower side down.
- To toss it up straight, - Is that so?
the x-axis and y-axis... My gosh.
- Do you make music with your brain?
- John.
- Don't you follow your heart?
Just do what feels right to you.
My gosh. The rotation...
How come it's not rotating?
- I got this.
- Why isn't it rotating?
(They must adopt to a new box for Round 2.)
Why isn't it rotating?
(Turning)
My box turned twice in the air.
Did you see that?
You know what else is important?
Balancing the box after it lands is crucial too.
Obviously.
It's not that obvious.
- Some people might not know that.
- That's so obvious.
I'm letting Park know that.
(Giggling)
We have to let the shock get absorbed.
- That's right. Just slightly.
- Slightly.
- It's like trapping a soccer ball.
- Let it absorb the shock.
- It's like trapping a ball.
We're trapping a box now.
I can't do it.
John is struggling with this round.
Wait. This counts too, right?
- I did it, right?
- John is struggling.
(John in a crisis)
My gosh. This is...
Because of him...
You're the breadwinner.
My gosh.
Round Two is already hard.
- So Round Three...
- This is hard.
The time limit will be the problem.
We have a lot of tries left.
Should we go for it?
- Shall we?
- Okay. Let's go.
Okay.
- Round 2.
Let's try Round Two.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Here we go!
- Here I go.
- Ready.
- No, hold on.
- Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 2.)
(2nd try)
Slowly.
(Now, it's John Park's turn.)
- Three, two, one.
- John or Park.
- Three...
- John...
- Three, two, one.
- John or Park.
(Second try failed)
- Park should go first.
- John...
- It's okay.
- Go first.
- John.
- No, don't.
- It's okay.
- We have many tries left.
- So far...
- There are many tries left.
- It's okay.
John should go first.
Let's change the order.
- Switch with me.
- Good. Okay.
This is really tough.
It's...
Toss it a little more gently, but move the reflector.
Okay.
Like so.
- You're really good at it.
- Look.
- It bounces too much.
- Move it to the edge.
Toss it gently, and then move the reflector.
That's it.
Okay.
(Succeeded)
- Okay. I've got the hang of it.
- Are you all set?
(John Park is getting the hang of it!)
(He succeeded again.)
I'm getting competitive.
Didn't you say it wouldn't get you excited?
- I thought it wouldn't.
- Are we ready?
(John Park is totally immersed.)
I've got the hang of it.
- All right.
- Let's do it.
Third try. We're on the third try, Round Two.
Let's all cheer together.
- Okay.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Go!
Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 3.)
(He succeeded right away.)
What? Seriously?
(John Park passed.)
(Woo Jae succeeded.)
(Jae Seok succeeded.)
(All that's left is Yeon Seok.)
We've got plenty of time.
One.
(Third try failed)
That was close.
- It's okay.
It's okay. We just have to nail it now.
Let's do it again right away.
- Yeon Shik...
- Woo Jae, why not go last?
By any chance, did you do that on purpose?
- Because...
- I would never.
In Whenever Possible I watched, Yoo One Shot...
- Yeon Seok...
- Go last, Woo Jae.
- It's different, right?
- I get nervous at times.
- Is that so?
- It's different, right?
- Isn't it different?
- Go ahead.
- Woo Jae, go last.
- What's more,
we all succeeded in one go.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- All right.
- I did it earlier.
Nice.
I'm not the type to choke under pressure.
Watch me. The moment we get to me...
Good.
- Do we go for it?
- All right. Let's do it.
- Really?
- Yes.
It's our fourth try, right?
In 1, 2, 3.
- Here we go!
Ready. Set.
(4th try)
Okay.
(All that's left is Woo Jae.)
Three...
Success!
(Woo Jae succeeded in one shot!)
(Cheering)
- Nice.
- Really.
- Well done.
- Good job.
- Nice.
- Yes.
We're on a roll.
- Nice.
- Amazing.
- Great.
- Honestly,
I can't say there's no pressure going last.
- It's nerve-racking.
- Yes, it's nerve-racking.
- Seriously, my heart was...
- It's nerve-racking.
It was stressful.
- Round Two, success!
- Success!
- Now then.
- Nice.
It'd be a waste not to go for Round Three.
We've got six tries left.
- There's also the chance.
- Correct.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Will you go for Round Three?
- You choose.
You can stop here.
Of course not.
Go!
- We have too many tries left.
- Let's see what Round Three is.
- We do.
- Okay.
It's Round Three.
Going last feels like I'm holding the whole world in my arms.
"The must-have class essential for showcasing..."
"all the techniques of a director..."
"who always sells out. LG StanbyME."
(Round 3 present: LG portable smart TV)
LG StanbyME is amazing.
(Director's must-have for class, Portable smart TV)
LG StanbyME.
- Is this a dream?
- It's...
(Making a grand entrance)
- The screen turns.
- It does.
What an amazing prize.
- You could watch vertically too.
- Yes.
- We really needed one.
- I see.
(Rustling)
If you fail...
- You lose everything.
- It hasn't been secured yet.
If you fail... Next time...
What's for Round Three?
Sorry? Why am I eating it?
- Aren't we done with these?
- We no longer need them.
- They're running low on sugar.
- We need some sugar.
- Should we go for it?
- Yes.
(Round 3)
(Make the box stand in a relay in one go)
You can't try again.
- With this box?
- Yes.
But Jae Seok opened his.
You shouldn't have opened it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Do you have another one?
- I'm sorry.
- Here.
- This is challenging.
- Okay.
What's challenging is that you can't fail.
(It's over if anyone fails.)
- There's no retry.
- In one go.
- In 1 go.
One, two...
- This one's tough.
- Right?
There's no time limit.
- But we have to succeed in one go.
- It's the end if the box falls.
Do we have to keep it standing?
In short, don't go wild...
- even if you succeed.
- No.
Just stay still.
Once you succeed, stay still.
- Move back.
- Keep it standing, right?
No, don't even move back.
- It...
- Just stand still.
There's much more pressure going first.
Both the first and last players have a great burden.
It's the end if the first player keeps failing.
It's over if the first player fails.
- Right?
- That's the end of the try.
- It's over.
- There's no retry.
We get no retries.
We're doing much better than expected.
Do you mind changing the box for me?
(Very sensitive)
The edge is slightly dented.
(Jae Seok isn't interested.)
(1st player John Park feels a lot more pressure.)
Are you fine with going fourth?
(Succeeded)
Hold on.
(Succeeded again)
I'm laser-focused.
- I've never been this focused.
- Should we try?
- No, I...
- Do you want to go fourth, Park?
Jae Seok, do you want to go first?
- Go 4th, Park.
- I'll go 4th.
- Go ahead, Park.
- Okay.
Get a taste of success.
- Is this okay?
- Let's do this.
He can totally do it. He can.
I have a good feeling right now.
- Be careful.
- If the first player fails,
- is it over?
- Yes.
- That's too much pressure.
- We have no time limit.
Right?
- I'm feeling the pressure.
- You'll get crushed.
Wait, it's kind of...
- It's a little...
- So going first is...
There. It's that look.
- That look.
- Right.
How about going first, Woo Jae?
Don't you feel confident right now?
(Jae Seok tries to get Woo Jae to go 1st.)
Give it a shot.
I'll try it, but only this time.
- Go ahead.
- Okay, try it.
(Scared, they change the order again.)
- Give me a second.
- I'm all set.
Ready?
- Okay.
- Shall we try?
Round Three.
It's our fifth try.
What? I'm not ready yet. Hold on.
Okay.
- Here we go.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Here we go!
Ready. Set.
We've got plenty of time.
(5th try, Woo Jae)
Failed.
(Fifth try failed)
(It ended right away.)
- It's okay.
- I'll go first.
- The thing is...
All four having to succeed puts...
- great pressure on us.
- Totally.
What's worse,
- we have to succeed in one go.
- Right.
- It's far from easy.
- This is...
(Sunken eyes)
- The AC...
- I can't go first.
- John is going first.
- Go...
- Go 4th.
- John is 1st.
- Fourth?
- Fourth.
John is first.
You get the pressure we feel, right?
These two are making the guests take on the tough roles.
We're letting you take them.
- Exactly.
- To make us the star?
- I see.
- For you to succeed.
We want you to get a taste of success.
- It's to make you the star.
- This is...
Do it boldly.
I do well during practice.
No, give me a second.
- Okay.
- I've got it.
Should we go for it? I have a good feeling.
- Let's go for it.
- Park has a good feeling.
Here we go!
Ready.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 6.)
- Here we go.
- Ready. Set.
There's no time limit.
(John calmly relocates the box.)
It's...
- Let me get it in place.
- We have no time limit.
(6th try, John Park)
Okay.
(6th try, Yeon Seok)
Nice.
(He made it stand!)
Nice. That was awesome.
Yeon Seok, that was awesome.
(6th try, Jae Seok)
You're the star right now.
Oh, my.
(6th try, Jae Seok)
(Sixth try failed)
(Dropping)
Are you playing badminton?
- Is this badminton?
- How frustrating.
(The worst play makes everyone furious.)
- But you practiced so much.
- Yeon Seok.
- You wanted me to fail, right?
- You see...
- Your success...
- My failing...
really stunned me.
- You...
- My...
- It's always...
- That was...
the first kind of move in all seasons.
Yeon Seok,
- what you did was incredible.
- Really.
- How you made it stand.
- It was amazing.
- There aren't many tries left.
- We must...
- Hold on.
- succeed.
I'll do my best. Ta-da.
All right. I'm set.
- Let's do this!
- Good luck!
- Go!
Don't think too much.
I just figured something out. May I share it?
- Yes.
- Will it get in your way?
- It will.
- Let's focus for now.
- If we...
- Listen.
Like golf, the address... What do you call it? The setup.
- It's the address.
- Take it long, and it works well.
- Long?
- Address it long,
and it works smoothly.
Do I take my time with the setup?
- Yes.
- It works.
Taking time with the setup works well.
- Can't you give it a shot?
It works.
Everyone has their own feel for it.
It works really well.
(Refusing the lesson)
- I'll use my own feel.
- Okay.
- Let's see who fails.
- Fine.
- I'll trust my own gut.
- Okay.
- Aren't we on the same team?
- I love it.
How can you say, "Let's see who fails?"
I'll trust my own gut.
- Why'd you have to jinx it?
- His...
His stubbornness shocked me.
Stubbornness?
- Let me practice.
- I'm all set, you know?
Let's change.
But really. If you take time,
- You feel some ease, right?
- the box stands.
- Okay, let's figure it out.
- This is mine.
Let's find our own way.
- We're all set.
- Let's try.
John Park, you get it, right?
Totally. I'm on a roll right now.
- Let's do this!
- Good luck!
Don't think too much.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
- I want to secure the prize.
- Here we go.
- Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 8.)
(8th try, John Park)
That's it.
- It's stable.
- Well done.
With confidence.
(8th try, Jae Seok)
Nice.
What if it's me?
(8th try, Yeon Seok)
Nice.
That was close.
(The last player is Woo Jae.)
Take your time.
You did well until now.
Address it long, and it works smoothly.
(Using the method he figured out earlier)
(8th try, Woo Jae)
Failed.
That little...
(Screaming)
Failed.
(The last player failed.)
I knew it the moment he started showing off.
(Woo Jae said he wouldn't get discouraged.)
That little... Really.
(But he's tasting the bitterest defeat of his life.)
It's the psychological pressure.
Because you saved what seemed like the impossible,
our expectations shoot up after going down.
- I don't die that easily.
- For real. It's amazing.
(You're the best, Yeon Seok.)
And so...
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- If you're busy...
- Woo Jae.
(Woo Jae is in a slump.)
You should've done it with confidence.
- We still have the chance left.
- We'll use it now.
Now? Okay.
- Pick one from here.
- Okay.
- An unlucky one is mixed in here.
- Pick one out carefully.
- Okay.
- I'm picking this one.
(What's the chance before the 9th try?)
"On this try,"
"one reflector becomes..."
- Stiff!
- "stiff."
(Lucky)
A stiff reflector?
- Nice one.
- This one's a lucky chance.
- It's...
- Thank you.
It looks way better.
(Normal reflector, Chance reflector)
Maybe the last player...
The last player should use it.
It's worse.
Let me try.
It's not easy.
Jae Seok, how about... I'll try it.
I can use it, right?
(Clean)
- That should do.
- All set.
We're set.
All good.
Okay, let's do this.
Is this order okay?
- The order is fine, right?
- Is it?
John Park can go last.
Let's do this.
(Woo Jae is lost right now.)
Get a grip, Woo Jae.
I lost my feel when I shared my tip...
with Park.
- I did well earlier.
- Right.
He's in a slump. Woo Jae's got the yips.
- Hold on.
- Yips?
- He's got the yips.
- Woo Jae, keep the setup small.
You can keep it small.
(Suddenly)
The setup...
- You're teaching me, right?
- Yes, go slow with the setup.
Don't take it long. Go slow.
- Keep it short.
- John or Park.
Toss it up slightly.
A long setup. Short setup. Like this.
That's it. But if you toss it up...
too high, the box bounces.
John Park's talking a lot now.
I know, right?
He's gotten the hang of it.
- That's it.
- We need to succeed this time.
- I'll go first.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Let's go!
- Let's do a group cheer.
- Here.
- It's a chance.
- Come. Let's cheer.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Go!
We have to succeed. We must succeed in this try.
It'd be bad if we fail.
- The next try will be our last.
- Let's go.
(The ninth try to break the bad streak)
This is...
Breaking out into a sweat is...
- hurting my pride.
- Woo Jae is nervous for real.
All right.
Okay.
- Let's go, Woo Jae!
- Okay.
I've been fighting my way through life!
- Let's go!
- Don't let it get to you.
You can do it. Give me a minute.
There's plenty of time.
- Here I go.
- Here we go.
- Ready. Set.
(Chance: New reflector, 9th try, Woo Jae)
Failed.
- It's okay!
I couldn't even use the chance.
It's okay!
I didn't even get a turn.
(The chance is gone.)
We should've had Woo Jae use it.
- For now...
- Yes?
- Go first, John Park.
- Okay.
Go first.
- Can you go fourth, Woo Jae?
- No.
He's become firm.
For now... Woo Jae.
Because you're not confident and being cautious,
you're unable to toss the box up.
I should place the box near the edge.
You're unable to toss it up.
- Yes, I'll place it near the edge.
- You have to toss it up.
The box won't fly like this.
You have to flick it up a little.
But the timing matters.
See?
You didn't get a turn yet.
- It's not like you're all that...
- Here. Look.
I'm good at it, you know?
(Laughing)
You're in big trouble now.
No, I need to come around.
(It'd be terrible if he made another mistake.)
We have to succeed.
The last try needs to end well.
- Let's do it.
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
- Good luck!
- It's our last try.
Please.
Please!
In this order?
I shouldn't have come on the show.
- Relax.
- I didn't think...
it'd stress me out this much.
- Are we ready?
- I'm set.
Let's go.
- Good luck.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Go!
(Good luck on the last try.)
- Here we go.
- Please.
- You're ready, right?
Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on the last try.)
(Last try, John Park)
(Last try, Jae Seok)
- Please.
- You can do it.
You can do it.
(It's the 3rd player, Woo Jae's turn.)
(Last try, Woo Jae)
(Even Woo Jae succeeded!)
(Last try, Yeon Seok)
(It's a success if Yeon Seok makes the box stand.)
Yeon Seok, you've always done it.
You're Yoo One Shot. You always succeed.
(The last try)
Don't shake it.
(And the last player)
Success!
(They've succeeded in the mission.)
(Yeon Seok did it.)
(They finally succeeded on the last try.)
(A miracle made by four people)
Thank you!
- Success!
- Nice!
Success!
And in the last minute. Amazing.
Look at Woo Jae.
(The Whenever Friends have passed out.)
Are you praying?
Earlier...
Earlier, he was skeptical about the joy we felt.
He was skeptical about how happy we get.
- Yeon Seok, thank you so much.
- What are you...
Really.
Thank you so much.
Round Three,
- success!
- Success!
(Succeeded Round 3 on the 10th try)
(Yoo One Shot lived up to his name.)
You feel drained, right?
(John or Park is exhausted.)
John or Park did a great job.
He was reliable.
- But really...
- How was it?
Gosh.
("I don't think I'll be that happy even if we succeed today.")
(By Joo Woo Jae 1 hour ago)
You didn't know why we got all happy.
To be frank, had we failed right now,
the guilt would've lasted for two months.
(Woo Jae has been saved.)
Really, I... Hold on.
Congratulations.
- Woo Jae...
- Thank you.
Woo Jae is soaked in sweat.
He's soaked in sweat.
(Done with this year's cardio)
With that, our guests...
get all the presents up to Round Three.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
(Gifting a coffee machine, air purifier, and portable TV)
- What is it, Woo Jae?
- I'm worried.
I've grown attached to them.
But I won't see them next week.
We've grown so close to each other.
- Already?
- There's a sense of camaraderie.
- We do feel a sense of camaraderie.
- Yes.
- We do.
- By the way, John was very calm.
- Gosh. Good job, everyone.
- What a start.
- He was great.
- Yes.
Once again, Bit Na,
- congratulations to both of you.
- Thank you.
Okay. How are you spending your precious spare time?
Whenever Possible Season 5, a natural dose of dopamine.
Join them at 5pm on Tuesdays.
It will begin now!
- Whenever Possible.
- Call us now.
(Send your letter to Whenever Possible now!)
We're off to a great start today.
- We had a great start.
- We'll enjoy lunch comfortably.
- That's right.
- Great spots are around here.
Right.
That's right, Woo Jae. Throughout your life,
- you need to stay humble.
- Exactly.
Keep that in mind. Okay?
The dopamine hits hard, right?
Yes. You don't need to watch shorts.
- Instead of watching shorts, - That's right.
- gather around and play this game.
- You're right.
- Anyway, we'll start again at 2pm.
- Shall we?
- We have an hour and a half.
- I'm feeling great so far.
- Let's enjoy our success and eat.
- Yes.
- Sounds good.
- Let's eat first and go.
- Of course.
- Yes.
What are we having?
- There are so many good options.
- Well.
How about pizza or burgers?
- Pizza?
- Should we go for Western food?
- Western food?
- Western food.
Western food sounds good once in a while.
- There's a really good pizza spot.
- Do you know the place?
- This one.
- Yes. I found that one too.
Should we go there? It's right next to us.
- It's right nearby.
- Yes. Let's go there.
- What do they have?
- Pizza.
- There's a great pizza spot.
- Sounds great.
- They sell Neapolitan pizza.
- I love it.
But there might be a queue.
- It's right nearby.
- Let's go and check.
We'll turn left now.
What? I don't see a queue.
- No?
- No.
What? Are they closed?
Are they closed?
Gosh. They open for lunch only on weekends.
They don't do lunch.
No wonder there was no queue.
Gosh. Pasta sounds good for the first time in a while.
Wait. I had pasta yesterday.
(They linger sadly in front of the restaurant.)
- What? It's raining.
- It's raining.
What did they have? Should I ask them?
Did you just eat?
- Yes.
- What did you have?
- We ate at our company cafeteria.
- At our cafeteria.
Your company cafeteria?
Their company cafeteria.
How's your company cafeteria?
- Why do you ask?
- Are you going to go there?
- He's a big fan of cafeterias.
- At your company? I see.
- Bye.
- Yes.
- Good luck.
- Let me search.
I don't need to search because they're all searching.
(The three younger ones start looking up restaurants.)
There's a great pork cutlet spot.
But I think there will be a line.
Wait. This is...
There's a barbecue place too.
I do like grilled meat,
but the smell will cling to us as it's raining.
Teppanyaki.
Teppanyaki doesn't sound good when it's raining.
Jae Seok is a type when asked what to have...
Didn't he step back,
- saying we were doing the search?
- Actually,
barbecuing is the only thing I'm reluctant about.
- We'll visit our next guest too.
- Right.
The tension will drop...
when we smell like barbecue.
- Is that so?
- Yes. A bit.
Western food, then?
- Anything's fine.
- Right up there,
- there's Kitchen 485.
- Sounds good.
(He's on board right away after hearing the name.)
Have I already told you about their menus?
What? I thought we were going there.
- They have lasagna, burrata...
- Great.
- They have oil-based pastas.
- Sounds great.
I think it'll cost about 200 dollars if we eat there.
- Sounds good.
- Is it an expensive spot?
- It's a bit costly.
- Let's go.
- Do you not feel confident?
- I'm fine.
- If you're scared, back out.
- I want to have expensive dishes.
- If you're scared, go somewhere...
- I love spending my money on shows.
- Let's go, then.
- Okay.
Let's go.
(They leave, acting tough.)
Gosh. Their wood-fired pizza looks good.
(Staring)
There was a cafe near here.
It was mentioned in one of 10cm's songs.
That cafe was right here.
I'm sorry, but I shot "Infinite Challenge" there.
Do I really have to mention that?
- I'll try many times today.
- Sure.
I shot "Infinite Challenge" there...
when 10cm came to the show.
(Sighing)
- It's an Italian restaurant.
- Italian.
It's right here.
- They make the pasta from scratch.
- Good.
- It's pretty.
- And there's no one here.
- Yes.
- Good.
Hello.
Where's the menu? It's this one.
We need to scan the QR code.
- Do we scan the QR code?
- Yes.
(Scanning the menu)
Gosh. This meal will cost us a bit.
- What? Wait.
- If you're scared...
- There's tenderloin steak.
- Are we having some steak?
- But...
- If you want to.
We should at least order one.
- We should order one.
- If you want to.
- Let's get a pizza.
- And a steak.
- And a risotto and two pastas.
- Sounds great.
I'll place our order here. I'll do it.
(Ordering a feast)
(Thinking)
I realized I like Yeon Seok...
- more than I thought.
- Why do you say that?
Come to think of it,
my all-time favorite music video is "Three of Us."
Considering that...
I co-starred in it with Gong Myoung.
Were you the bad guy again?
- No. He loses the girl.
- He loses her.
I have a crush on this girl, but my friend wins her over.
They get married.
And I play the piano at the wedding.
What a nice guy.
(Yeon Seok, the nice guy, 12 years ago)
You watched lots of my work.
I know. I just realized that too.
Recently, people around me have been saying...
that they love Woo Jae.
So many of my friends said so.
- Right.
- Then...
Tell them.
- So I...
- Tell them what?
What? To take a good look at him again.
He's driving me nuts.
They find him so funny.
He's funny while being so stylish at the same time.
He has the body for variety shows.
He's born with it.
When I saw him play the game just now,
I thought he was good in the beginning.
He was really good in the beginning,
but like you said, Jae Seok,
- he wasn't persistent.
- You're right.
- He can't keep up for long.
- He lacks endurance.
- He lacks stamina.
- Yes.
Mentally, I can't keep up for long.
Right. You collapse.
Still, we did a great job.
It was really...
That was really intense.
- Park maintained his pace.
- He was really good.
You were reliable.
- Thank you.
- Going first wasn't easy.
- He's very calm.
- Yes.
That plays a big role in a game like this.
I get worked up easily.
- Did you just yawn?
- Yes. I was bored.
Did you yawn when I was talking?
- He really yawned.
- Yes.
He yawned deeply. I saw it too.
(Laughing)
By the way,
- you're close with Lee Juck.
- Yes.
You laugh like him.
- Do I?
- Yes.
- When I laugh in a high pitch?
- When I laugh like this.
- Yes.
Me?
He and Juck have the same laugh.
- I have a witch's cackle like him.
- I see.
- They've been friends for so long.
- Yes.
When you spend lots of time together, you become alike.
- That happens.
- Yes.
What?
I brought my wallet just in case.
And that will become the case.
We'll see about that.
- Which game are we playing?
- What should we play?
Today...
How about spinning the knife?
- It spins really well.
- It does.
This is perfect.
- Let's spare the one it points at.
- Shall we?
- Shall we decide before we eat?
- It's a game of chance.
- When we eat, - Let's do it afterward.
we should feel comfortable.
- Let's spare 1 person.
- Only 1 person eats comfortably.
- Only one?
- Yes.
- Sounds good.
- Only one will eat comfortably.
- Good.
Let's spin it. One will be saved.
Okay.
I'll spin it.
It has to be me.
- It should be me.
- I want to eat comfortably.
I just want to enjoy the meal.
We'll spare one person.
- I have a good feeling today.
- It pointed at me before.
(Who will be the lucky 1 person who gets to eat in peace?)
It's me.
(Jae Seok is exempt from paying for the meal.)
Darn it.
(Thrilled)
Gosh. It's no fun.
I brought my wallet, though.
(It's super fun.)
Gosh. Thanks to the younger ones,
- Darn.
- I'm at an Italian restaurant...
after a long time.
- Is it all right?
- We have no problem paying for it.
But hearing him speaking like that throughout the meal...
We have to keep hearing it.
That's the problem.
The satisfied look on his face bothers me so much.
What? It's here.
- Thank you.
Let's forget about the game we just played.
Why don't we see who can stretch the cheese the longest?
I'll take a piece now.
You three can decide.
- It's on us.
- Yes.
- You can pick one first.
- Anything's fine.
Is this condensed milk? You can dip it in honey.
The cheese pizza.
(Satisfied)
It's good.
(Finally recharging the energy spent on the game)
- It's tasty, isn't it?
- Yes.
I'm hungry.
(Finally recharging the energy spent on the game)
- It's good.
- It's tasty.
(Stretched cheese)
It tastes so good because I haven't had it in a while.
It tastes even better since it's been a while.
Exactly.
- Gosh.
- It's so good.
The wood-fired Gorgonzola pizza is so good.
Gosh. You're really enjoying it.
It's flavorful.
(Overreacting)
I don't want you to enjoy it so much.
It's so tasty.
It tastes even better as it's free.
It's free.
It tastes better when it's free.
(After having the free pizza...)
The pasta noodles already look good.
(Giving it to Yeon Shik first)
Right. You should at least serve it when you're not paying.
Have just a little bit because you might pay, Woo Jae.
(Enjoying the meal more than anyone)
They must've learned how to cook it in Italy.
(Yeon Seok and Park focus on the meal,)
(forgetting about the bet.)
I can totally smell the prawns.
(And here's the one staying away from the table.)
(Chewing half-heartedly)
It's good.
I think Woo Jae's full.
I'm ready to play the next game.
Right?
Come to think of it,
I'm a member of SBS now.
- Why?
- What do you do?
Season Two of "The Ballad of Us" starts in October.
I'm part of Top-100 Ears, the word you made up.
- Congratulations.
- Gosh. It's really...
Many teenagers are on the show.
- I see.
- It must be touching.
- It's really moving.
- I bet.
Many people have so many desperate stories.
They're such good singers too.
There are so many good singers in Korea.
- You're right.
- There are so many.
Koreans are...
naturally gifted at singing.
They're so good.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
(Finishing it with a smoky and buttery flavor)
- Goodness.
- Thank you.
We have to have our proteins.
You'll get a bite at least, right, Woo Jae?
Just a tiny bit.
It's well cooked.
It looks good.
The meat is really cooked well.
When I look at the meat, I can tell.
(The meat lets him forget that he's full.)
Gosh, Woo Jae. You have to have it.
Yes. You have to eat it.
- It's tasty.
- It's cooked so well.
Every dish tastes great here.
(Savoring)
Gosh.
(Taking another bite even though he's full)
You're eating quite a bit today.
- Yes.
- Because he might pay for it.
- That's why.
- He doesn't hesitate to eat.
In fact, I'm shoving it in a bit.
- Because I might pay for it.
- You should.
Like I always said, if you're scared, get out.
Woo Jae...
I can picture him getting the knife.
- At the end?
- Yes. Like this.
I can see the knife pointing at you.
- I'll spin it.
- Okay.
The person it points to will pay.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
(Whoever the knife points to will pay for the meal.)
(The stakes got higher after ordering the steak.)
It won't be me.
(The knife points to...)
- What?
- It's Woo Jae.
Goodness.
(Woo Jae will pay.)
- This is amazing.
- I was correct.
(Happier than anyone else)
The picture I saw...
- That was exactly it.
- Gosh.
My gut has been spot-on lately.
- Woo Jae treats me a lot.
- Woo Jae will pay for the meal.
- Thanks for the meal.
- Thanks for lunch, Woo Jae.
- Thank you.
- Gosh, Woo Jae.
- Woo Jae.
- You'll pay because you lost.
- Thank you.
I'll go and brush my teeth.
Gosh. I'm full.
Why am I sleepy?
I'm getting a blood sugar spike.
(A food coma hits after a hearty meal.)
They gave us candies to refresh our palates.
- Let's try them.
- It wakes you up, right?
Have it when you're sleepy after a meal.
- I'm a bit sleepy.
- Right.
- I'm drowsy.
- Take one when you're drowsy.
Gosh. Is menthol the refreshing ingredient?
We're supposed to eat it like this.
We're really supposed to eat it like that.
You crunch into it.
Crunch.
- Gosh. I love its texture.
- It's tasty.
It clears my nose at once.
I'm totally awake now.
- This...
- It woke me right up.
- We need to stay alert.
- Yes.
We need to be fully awake to play the second game.
We can play the game after taking this one.
- Let's pull it off.
- I'm fully awake now.
(Woo Jae pays.)
- Did you enjoy the meal?
- Yes, it was so good.
It would've tasted even better if I didn't pay for it.
We can hop in that one.
- This one?
- Yes.
- Woo Jae treated us well.
- Gosh. I'm full.
(Going to the next spare time spot in the cab Navi Yoo called)
- Woo Jae.
- I feel great.
Thank you so much for lunch...
- at the Italian restaurant.
- You enjoyed it...
- more than anyone.
- It was really good.
It kept hitting my palate.
(Laughing)
If Woo Jae went there alone, he would've ordered only one dish.
- Gosh.
- One dish would be enough.
He'd only have one pasta.
I could keep it under 12 dollars.
Are you just going to have the complimentary bread?
A few pieces would be enough.
We'll do our best at our next spot.
Gosh. I'm nervous again. This is bad.
My stomach starts to hurt from nervousness.
Really?
Actually, Park.
You don't really get nervous.
I've been on a lot of survival shows.
I think I do better...
- in nervous situations.
- I think you do.
- You looked relaxed.
- That's right.
He should've had a breakdown.
- He's like that.
- But he stood strong.
When I played games...
- on other shows, - Yes.
the clutch time would arrive, and I...
- Did you become calmer?
- I did well.
Without any tension,
- I kind of fizzle out.
- I see.
Gosh. It'll make a great picture if this comment...
and him failing at the end are edited together.
- Right. This is...
- Yes.
I don't know how they'll use what I just said.
- It's...
- From an editing perspective...
That would be the perfect editing.
John, what we say often comes true on this show.
I think I owned Chapter One.
- And you'll own Chapter Two.
- Really?
I excel in clutch situations.
Yes, I'm confident.
We'll see.
Gosh. This place.
When I first came to Seoul...
after getting accepted into Hongik University,
I had to come here...
to find a place to live.
But we didn't have apps for that back then.
Woo Jae, this is Hapjeong Station, Exit Five...
where my song was created.
- Really?
- I was talking about my school.
This is Hapjeong Station, Exit Five.
- I see.
- I was going to talk...
about my heartbreaking twenties.
Woo Jae, this is Hapjeong Station, Exit Five.
- Hapjeong Station, Exit Five - Hapjeong Station, Exit Five
- It's over there.
- We're here.
- Is it across from here?
- Yes.
We'll get there after making a left turn.
- Will we get there?
- Yes.
"Lee Su Hee and Roh Si Hyeon."
"ESTJ and INFP."
"We overcame our polar opposite personalities..."
- "to become business partners."
- That's not easy.
"We've been friends for 34 years since high school."
"In the basement where neither the present perfect tense..."
"nor the quadratic formula works,"
"we've been waiting for customers for nine months."
"Will you be our light of hope, Whenever Possible?"
Gosh. As soon as I heard their story,
- it broke my heart.
- Yes.
They're waiting for customers in the basement for nine months.
- Do they run their own business?
- Exactly.
They mentioned...
the present perfect tense and the quadratic formula.
- Is it about English and math?
- Yes, math.
Are they connected to those?
Thank you, sir.
(They're getting out near the spare time spot.)
Hold on. It's one of these spots.
- Where is it?
- Hold on.
(Navi Joo is on.)
It's this one.
- Yes.
- Here.
But...
It doesn't look like the basement I expected.
- It's here.
- What is this place?
- It's vegan...
- What?
- It's also a pasta place.
- Wait.
- We just had pasta.
- They said...
they're in the basement, so this must be it.
Why did we have pasta, then?
- What? We should've eaten here.
- We should've helped them.
They have pizza too.
We should've eaten here and played the game right away.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
- Their menu...
- is the same.
- They sell the same thing.
We should've eaten here.
- Exactly.
- We can play the game right away.
It's cheaper here. Gosh.
- Gosh!
- For goodness' sake.
- Goodness.
- They scared me.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- This place is quite big.
- Welcome.
- Goodness.
- Hello.
- My goodness.
- Are you Lee Su Hee?
- Hello.
- Gosh.
- Yes.
- Are you Roh Si Hyeon?
- Yes, I am.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Gosh.
- My goodness.
Is this an Italian restaurant?
Yes, it is.
Actually, we...
We just had our lunch at an Italian restaurant in Hongdae.
Italian? We sell Italian food too.
Exactly. You have the same menu.
- We should have eaten here.
- We should've come here.
You're an INFP, and you're an ESTJ.
- Is it the other way around?
- Yes.
- You're an ESTJ. You're an INFP.
- I'm so happy to see you.
- Hello.
Gosh.
- Nice to meet you.
- I can't believe it.
- This is a very big place.
- I'm going crazy.
- That's right.
- It's huge.
- The vibe will be awesome at night.
- Yes.
This is a nice space.
Thanks for the compliment.
You've decorated it so well.
- Yes.
- Thank you so much.
(Whenever Guests' touch can be seen throughout the restaurant.)
You've been friends for 34 years.
That's right.
When I came in here, it was different...
from the basement I expected...
where you would await the customers to come.
- That's right.
- I thought it'd be dark.
- It was different.
- I see.
It's very...
- It's very big.
- And it's bright.
I expect you'd have many customers here.
But it's less exposed,
compared to the restaurants on the ground level.
Once they're here, they're satisfied.
They're happy here, and they come back.
But we don't get new customers.
- I see.
- No new customers.
They go, "Where is this place?"
- That's right.
- They can't find the place.
That's the reason.
- That's right.
- So, we have lots of spare time.
We just stare up there.
- Where?
- There.
We get so happy when customers come down.
You wait eagerly for customers from here.
- That's right.
- Over there.
I stare at it like this.
(Desperate)
Did you run a restaurant before this?
We ran a cafe before.
But not many people were around.
So, we moved here because there are more people.
- I see.
- But we didn't know...
running a business in the basement would be this hard.
- You ran a cafe somewhere else.
- Yes.
And I assume you moved here because it was booming.
We moved to succeed.
- To succeed.
- Yes.
(I see.)
- Suddenly...
- Is it enough...
Is it enough to keep the restaurant running?
- We can't keep it running.
- No?
How are you running it when you can't?
We're investing...
- lots of our money.
- It's an investment for you.
Yes. That's what we're doing.
Is that why you sent the letter to our show?
I guess our friends felt sorry for us.
- Pardon?
- Since we have so much spare time,
our friends kept urging us to do it.
So we thought we'd go for it as our friends kept urging us.
(Their high school alumni suggested they do it.)
Is this your spare time right now?
- Yes.
- The time after lunch.
- That's right.
- Right.
We have a short lunch time.
We open at 11:30am.
Around 1pm or 1:30pm,
- We don't have any customers.
- the customers are gone.
Our break starts at 3pm,
- but from 2pm...
- We have spare time.
- I see.
- You kept looking over there.
I get so happy when they walk down the stairs.
What made you open this restaurant?
We were in the same class in our first year of high school.
We weren't that close back then.
We had opposite personalities.
And she slept a lot. I couldn't really remember her.
- Yes. She was tired.
- I'm an INFP.
- She slept a lot.
- She's an INFP.
When I went to school,
I talked a lot with my friends.
But I don't remember talking to her because she was sleeping.
But she speaks good English.
I used to run a math academy.
- I see.
- When she came back from the US,
I got back in touch with her, and we worked together.
- Hence the present perfect tense...
- The present perfect tense.
- and the quadratic formula.
- That's right.
- I see.
- Yes.
(Roh Si Hyeon, Lee Su Hee)
(They met in high school 34 years ago.)
(Lee Su Hee, Roh Si Hyeon)
(Roh Si Hyeon, Lee Su Hee)
(The two classmates from the girls' high school...)
(have partnered up since the tutoring academy.)
While running the tutoring academy,
I thought everything would work out if I do it with her.
While we have different personalities,
- we complement each other.
- That's true.
Do both of you cook?
- I'm the only one cooking.
- Yes. Both of us used to cook.
But we couldn't agree on some points.
So we separated our roles.
What was the conflict mainly about?
She's so creative.
She's too creative. When it came to our menus,
I wanted to choose a few dishes...
and develop those immensely.
But she kept coming up with new dishes.
She expanded the menu...
- with various dishes.
- That's right.
Sometimes, I found out about the new dish after I got here.
I didn't know about the new dishes.
- No wonder.
- She couldn't really watch it.
When I walked downstairs, I saw all sorts of dishes.
I've never even heard of K-dessert pizza before.
They have more stuff than a convenience store.
I couldn't even read everything.
All I can think of are new dishes.
- You keep thinking about new ones.
- Yes.
When doing business together, even close friends can fight.
- They cut ties.
- They don't see each other again.
They say not to go into business with your friend.
That's right. They say that.
They need to get along like them to do business.
But I think we've overcome our differences well.
We've talked to each other a lot.
We tried to see each other's strengths.
- That's right.
- Yes.
She has always been the popular one.
She gets along well with customers too.
- I guess she's very likable.
- I see.
- They love her.
- She's an ESTJ.
- They like her very much.
- She's an extrovert.
Yes, that's right.
Yes. Thank you.
She's a dear friend.
Anyway, since we're here...
I mean, it's raining outside too.
- We need to get you presents.
- For the two of you,
- This is driving me nuts.
- we will...
- Let's start Round One.
- My goodness.
Let's go from there.
You do it.
(Letting her best friend to do it)
Will she develop a new dish with that?
- With the fortune cookie?
- I've already thought about it.
Have you already thought about it?
Yes.
You are full of ideas.
- What is it?
- "We fight when working."
"But we're best friends..."
- "when shopping."
- It's a gift certificate.
"A 300-dollar Hyundai Department Store Gift Certificate."
(It's perfect for them as they love shopping.)
- Bravo.
- Nice.
(Best buddies when shopping)
(A 300-dollar department store gift certificate)
- They're so thrilled.
- A 300-dollar gift certificate...
- Yes.
- for Hyundai Department Store.
- You love it, don't you?
- We love it.
- You love it.
- Yes.
(Flying Pizzas)
(Throw a disc using a pizza peel...)
(to cover the pizzas.)
(Round 1: Cover 2 out of 4 pizzas.)
(Time limit: 20 seconds)
What is it?
(Targets)
- We're supposed to cover them.
- I didn't know about this game.
We have to cover those pizzas completely.
- Do we only cover the pizzas?
- Yes.
Gosh. This is tough again.
This won't be easy.
It's...
This is hard.
(Flustered)
This is how you should do it.
(It didn't cover the slice at all.)
Gosh. This is...
- We need to throw it gently.
- It's really tough.
Does it have to flip in the air?
- Gosh.
- We have to practice a lot.
My goodness. Didn't they do well during practice, though?
- Yes. When I watched it on TV, - Oh dear.
they always pulled it off during practice.
- This is way too hard, though.
- It's so tough.
It worked.
It covered the slice.
Look at me.
Instead of throwing it, push it forward.
See? This is how it goes.
We have to push it forward.
Like this.
- Okay.
- Good.
(Okay!)
- It worked.
- This is how it's done.
- This is the vibe.
You have to be gentler than you think.
We have to throw it lower.
(Setting his foot)
Like this.
- Okay.
- Hey, it worked.
- It's working.
- It's feasible.
- Okay.
- It works after a while. Okay.
- I got it.
- Gosh.
- They got it.
- My goodness.
- Good.
- Let's go for it.
- Let's go.
- Let's cheer up.
- Let's huddle up.
- Okay.
- One, two, three.
- Let's go.
- Here we go.
- Ready.
- Let's go.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
Let's be confident.
- Gosh.
- Darn it.
(1st try)
(Is it a success?)
- Didn't he pull it off?
- What?
(It's slightly sticking out.)
Gosh. It's sticking out a bit.
(Both of them have to pull it off.)
- Didn't he pull it off?
- It's sticking out a bit.
- Gosh.
- It's over.
(First try failed)
- Gosh.
- It's over.
(Their first try failed in vain.)
I should have pulled it off.
This always happens in the actual game.
- Isn't this a pass?
- No, it's not.
Who eats the whole slice?
Everyone leaves a bit of pizza...
- when you're having a slice.
- It's a leftover.
- Let's do it again.
- You don't eat the crust.
- This is the angle.
- It worked.
- Throw it.
- Okay.
- It worked.
- He did it.
It works so fine. Why didn't it work before?
Gosh. It's so frustrating.
Everyone does so well during practice.
Let's go. Let's do this.
- Go!
- Let's go!
- Go.
- Let's go.
- This is our 2nd try.
- It's our 2nd try.
Here we go.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 2.)
- Do it with confidence.
- Ready.
(2nd try)
Darn it.
This is driving me nuts.
- We're doomed.
- This is a practice, then.
- Park.
- Yes.
Park, you should go first.
It just won't work. Why does it go so well during practice, though?
- We're all on fire during practice.
- Why won't it work?
Gosh. We're doomed.
- Should we change the order?
- You should go first.
Look at me, Yeon Seok.
Slightly lower the angle.
And you push it.
Would you do it like that during the actual game?
It's perfect.
- Don't mess it up.
- Don't tilt it upward.
- Lower it and push it.
- Do you have a license to teach?
You taught us like that before, then you failed.
- Should we go for it?
- Hold on.
Let's gather our hands together.
- Let's go.
- Let's huddle up for a cheer.
- Let's do this.
- By doing the cheer,
I'm losing my energy.
Then get out.
Stay out of it.
- Don't do it.
- We should do it together, though.
One, two, three.
- Let's do it.
- Gosh. Hold on.
- You have to pull it off. Let's go.
- We're on our third try already.
- Go.
You can do this.
Here we go.
Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 3.)
(3rd try)
Okay.
(The first slice is completely covered.)
(Yeon Seok is up next.)
- Nice.
- We did it!
(It landed perfectly.)
- Nice.
- We did it!
- We did it.
- Yes.
Hey, Jae Seok.
- Nice.
- We did it!
We did it.
Hey, Jae Seok.
- We did it.
- That was great.
- It's our first win.
- Gosh.
- Round One,
- success.
- Success.
- Nice.
- Gosh.
- We are good at this.
- He's good.
- Okay.
- Good job.
I get it now.
- Okay. Now, - Yes.
you have to decide if you want to move on to Round Two.
Go.
- Go.
- We're still doing okay.
- Okay. Round Two.
- You should go for it.
"For the fashionista owners of the restaurant..."
"who dream of dominating Hongdae with pizzas,"
"two WOOYOUNGMI shirts."
(Screaming)
- They're expensive.
- Their designer shirts.
- They're WOOYOUNGMI shirts.
They're expensive.
(Round 2 present: 2 designer shirts)
My goodness.
How did you know I love WOOYOUNGMI brand?
- Gosh.
- It's her favorite brand.
What's for Round Two?
(Round 2)
(Cover the whole pizza.)
(From 1 person covering 1 slice...)
The size got bigger.
Are we joining forces?
(Each gets 1 chance to throw.)
The size gets bigger.
- The discs must be small.
- We get 20 seconds.
- Then...
- Let me show you.
- We can finish it fast.
- I think they can do it.
- That's it.
- Like this.
I covered quite a bit.
(The first bite went smoothly.)
- They can do it.
- As for this round,
-They'll pull it off.
- I think they'll pull it off.
- That's it.
- Yes. Good.
And Park puts it over there.
The last disc...
- The last one.
- Yeon Seok puts it there.
- Gosh. That happens.
- Then we fail.
(Sticking out)
- Okay.
- I think they'll pull it off.
Gosh. It's not easy, though.
We have to cover the uncovered part.
(Teamwork is the key for Round 2.)
Woo Jae, do you want to go last to cover the remaining area?
Yes.
We still have a lot to cover. Try it.
Go for that part.
- Go, Park.
- John or Park.
In the end, the last player holds the key.
(Failed)
- But...
- It's not going to be easy.
- In the end...
- It's tough.
- Should we go for it?
- Let's try it.
Let's go for it.
I'll go fourth.
I'll go third.
- Okay.
- Do you want to go first?
- I'll go 1st, then.
- Go 1st.
- I'll go 1st.
- Then I'll go 2nd.
Okay.
(Now, it's team event to eat the pizza.)
Let's do it.
- Go!
- Shall we?
Why do I sweat whenver I play a game?
Here we go.
Ready. Set.
(4th try)
- It's covered.
- That's good enough.
- Good.
I'll finish it.
(4th try)
Hold on!
- Hold on!
- That didn't end it.
Gosh! Hold on.
It's up to you.
(4th try)
A lot of it is covered!
- Yes!
(Perfect)
(Jae Seok's neat finish)
- Yes!
- What?
- Did he do it?
- Gosh!
Did he do it?
- Nice!
- Gosh!
- It's our lucky day.
- What?
- This is hard to do.
- It's our lucky day.
- What was that?
- Gosh!
- Oh, my gosh!
- All right.
- Gosh!
- Round 2, success!
Gosh, that hurt.
- We passed Round Two.
- Oh, my gosh! That was amazing.
- We have...
- Which try was that?
- Two?
- six tries left.
- The chance can also be used.
- Oh, my gosh.
- We're so good.
- It will get harder from here.
Everything will be taken away if we fail.
Decide if you will go or stop. One, two, three.
- Go!
Gosh, it's the ESTJ.
It will be amazing if we pass Round Three twice in a row.
"The first friendship item for the ones..."
"who have shared the joys and sorrows of life for 34 years."
- "Two Dior friendship rings!"
- Gosh!
- What?
- Luxury brand rings?
(This is incredible!)
- Dior rings?
- That's amazing.
- What's going on today?
- Gosh.
WOOYOUNGMI and Dior.
- Even Hyundai Department Store.
- Gosh. Hold on!
Hold on!
- It isn't yours yet.
- Gosh!
All right.
- We're doing great right now.
- Right.
- Nice!
- Let's do this.
- We're doing great.
- Round Three!
- Let's do a cheer!
- Let's go!
- Yes!
- One, two, three. Let's go!
We didn't even hear about the game.
- What is it?
- We got this.
- What is it for Round Three?
- I think we can do it.
(Round 3)
(The pizza gets bigger.)
- Okay.
- From here?
- The pizza got bigger.
- Gosh!
- It's much bigger.
- It's...
- This must be done as a team.
- As if it's four slices each.
- Right.
Is this possible? Let's try.
- Can it get covered?
- I think it can get covered.
- Three must be thrown well.
- But...
- This is really hard.
- All four will be needed.
- But...
- Wasn't that perfect?
That was great, Jae Seok!
- I'll go for the left.
- Nice!
You should go last.
- It will get thrown to the middle.
- All right!
- Park will throw it to the right.
- Park!
- Done!
- Then...
That's perfect!
This is good enough.
This game is really exciting.
How did they come up with this one?
(The game feels exciting as they're doing well.)
- It's exciting.
- It feels new.
It feels new.
- You can do this.
- Let's go for it.
- All right.
- We can do this.
- I think they will make it.
- Let's go for it.
- Let's do a cheer.
- Here we go!
- Gosh!
- All right.
- Please!
- I have to cover as much as I can.
(5th try)
- Gosh, that's a lot.
- Nice!
- That's a lot!
Nice!
- Nice! Gosh!
- Gosh!
- It got folded! Gosh!
- What's that?
Why did it get folded?
- It got folded! Gosh!
- What do we do with that?
- Why did it get folded?
- Throw it up there and cover it.
Throw it to the front and cover it.
Hey!
You have to hit that one as well.
(5th try)
(Failed)
- That one got folded.
- Gosh!
- It got folded. Gosh.
- It's okay!
- It got folded.
- We have many tries left.
- Gosh.
- If it didn't get folded...
- Gosh!
- I thought it was going to work.
- This is tough.
Jae Seok is struggling.
Jae Seok ruined everything.
I'm sorry.
Gosh.
- My hands are sweaty.
- They can do this.
- It's making my hands sweaty.
- I think they can do this.
- It can't get folded.
It can't get folded.
A lot of it must get covered at the start.
- Shall we go for it?
- This is our sixth try.
- Let's go!
- Here we go.
- He's an important figure.
- But he ruins the small things.
- Ready.
Set.
(6th try)
- Nice!
- That was good, right?
Nice!
(6th try)
- That was great.
- Not bad!
- Throw it to the bottom.
- That was great.
- To the bottom.
- It should go to the bottom.
- Gosh!
- Gosh, it was slightly...
(Screaming)
- Like this?
- Five, four...
(Sixth try failed)
- Okay.
- There's still a chance.
- If this happens...
- That can't happen.
- One side has to be fully covered.
- That was so close.
It can't leave one side open.
- It can't leave one side open.
- That was close.
- We have 4 tries left.
We have four tries left.
- Would you like to start, Woo Jae?
- Should I start?
- The first one matters most.
- Right. Give it a try.
- Okay.
- I like going later.
- Park will go last?
- Okay.
- Right. Park will go last.
- Woo Jae will go first.
- I'll give it a try.
- Here we go!
Ready. Set.
(7th try)
(The best start)
- Gosh, that was great!
- Gosh!
- So much of it is covered.
- All right. Yeon Seok.
- Nice!
This is a big chance.
(7th try)
- Nice. Cover each side.
- Cover each side.
Cover each side.
(Jae Seok is next.)
- Nice. Cover each side.
- Cover each side.
- Cover each side. You have no time!
(Why aren't you throwing it?)
- I'm not sure if...
- You have no time!
I'm not sure if I should cover the top or bottom.
- We don't have time.
- Five, four...
- three, two, one.
- Gosh!
(Failed)
- One.
- Gosh!
I'm sorry, but why would you do that when we're short on time?
Why were you standing here and looking at us?
- We only had 20 seconds left.
- Gosh.
This is really hard.
- I didn't know where to throw it.
- It's hard.
- I said I do better in tough spots.
- We have two tries left.
- We'll use the chance. Time out!
- Hold on!
You might pick a bad one.
But there are a lot more that are good.
Done. Go for it.
- Please read it for us.
- Done.
- It's green.
- Is the green one bad?
"Lucky!"
"The pizza will get smaller for this try!"
(Lucky: The pizza will get smaller for this try.)
- Gosh!
- Yes!
- We can do this.
- Nice!
- Yes!
- That's really nice.
- The chance...
This is it.
- Very nice.
- All right.
- One slice got removed.
This is a big chance.
(A great chance to finish the game)
We must have the same mindset as earlier.
- Right.
- But if this happens...
(He covered the part that was removed.)
Yeon Seok covered the part that didn't need to be covered.
- Hold on.
- For this to work...
This is what's important.
It's the worst if it gets covered like this.
- That's the worst.
- Right.
It's the worst habit to think about the worst...
before getting to work.
- I didn't mean to do that.
- Got it?
(He gives him life advice all of a sudden.)
Right.
This is a big chance.
You picked a really good chance.
- What's the order?
- Let's go!
- But for this try...
- Gosh!
- We can't do that!
- That's the worst!
- We can't do that.
- That will be the worst.
Right. That's the worst.
We don't want to think about the worst, but you just...
- You made us think about the worst.
- Right.
- That's the worst.
- You made the worst play.
- You should go first, Woo Jae.
- I'll give it a try.
- Are you ready?
- No. I'll throw it to the left.
- Around this much.
- Right.
- That was nice.
- That will be enough.
- Nice.
- Let's go for it now.
- All right.
- Gosh, I feel so nervous.
- Right.
- Here we go!
Ready. Set.
(9th try, Chance: Pizza reduced)
- Done!
- Gosh!
- Hurry up, Jae Seok!
- Me?
Take one side each.
- Hurry up, Jae Seok!
- Me?
Take one side each. Jae Seok!
Nice!
This is driving me crazy.
(Just one side is left.)
(9th try, Chance: Pizza reduced)
- My gosh.
- You're doing a great job!
- Hold on.
- This side!
It's possible!
(John Park is the last one to go.)
Five, four,
three...
- Hold on.
- There wasn't enough time.
(An accident occurs.)
Three...
- Hold on.
- There wasn't enough time.
- Gosh.
But...
But this part...
can be seen anyway.
I saw this part.
You're saying that because you feel embarrassed.
It wasn't my fault!
We failed anyway.
- Did you hear what he said?
- What did he say?
- "Gosh, it wasn't my fault!"
- It can be seen.
- We failed anyway.
- That was exactly what he said.
"Gosh, it wasn't my fault!"
We should've made it during this try.
This was our chance.
The last...
Gosh.
It's the last try.
Gosh!
It's the last try!
Please!
(They reached the tenth try in the end.)
It's the last try!
- They can do it on the last try.
- You can do this.
- The tables will be turned.
- We made it on our last try.
Earlier, we made it on our last try.
Don't lose hope.
- Let's go!
- It's the last try.
- We'll do our best.
- Let's do this.
- We can do this.
- Okay. One, two, three.
- One, two, three.
- Let's go!
- Go!
- Woo Jae!
Let's do this.
- Let's become heroes.
- This is the perfect scene.
Let's become heroes.
Here we go!
It's the last try. Ready.
(He's an important figure.)
(Last try)
- Gosh!
- What?
(Jae Seok refuses to eat all of a sudden.)
(The other three must cover the pizza.)
- Gosh!
- It isn't over yet.
It isn't over yet. We can do this!
(It isn't over yet. We can do this!)
(Yeon Seok is the third person.)
Let's become heroes.
(The last one is meaningless.)
One.
(Failed overall)
- It's over?
- What did you just do?
But...
I felt so happy.
Do you like the crust?
Why did you get only the crust?
So...
They're taking everything back!
The WOOYOUNGMI...
Just a moment. Get a good shot of this.
This was Jae Seok's attempt.
- This one.
- But...
- Were you sick of eating pizza?
- I was the only one...
- Gosh!
- It's okay.
- to say, "Here we go."
- Gosh!
What?
- You still said it.
- But...
don't we say it together?
The younger ones didn't agree to start.
Didn't the production crew not accept our call?
That's not true.
It's okay!
- It's okay!
- Thank you. We had a blast.
- Thank you.
- This is our merch.
- I can't believe it.
- Gosh.
This isn't from WOOYOUNGMI, but I came up with the design.
- Really?
This is the Y from Yoo Yeon Seok.
- Gosh!
- This isn't from WOOYOUNGMI,
but I came up with the design.
- Gosh, it holds a special meaning.
- Right.
- It was tough.
- Thank you.
There was a sense of pressure toward the end.
- It was hard.
- It was really hard.
Using the chance was the best moment.
Right. It was so close.
(Woo Jae feels a lot of regret.)
Thank you so much!
- Thank you!
- Thank you so much.
- We're sorry.
- Gosh!
Gosh, it's okay.
It's fine.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be!
(They came through the heavy rain.)
(Whenever Friends of the same age, Yoo Seung Ho, Young K)
(A warm friendship that makes you smile naturally)
(There's a rough friendship next to them.)
Go for it, Young Hyun!
(In front of the breathtaking Whenever Missions,)
(the two friendships become one with comradeship.)
(He's on his knees!)
(If it doesn't work out,)
(make an argument...)
(and shed tears.)
(What do I do?)
(I can't say, "Here I go.")
(A hero steps up...)
(during tough times.)
(You did it, Seung Ho!)
(He does well under pressure!)
(Welcome to the dopamine show.)
(Whenever Possible Season 5)